THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS, TRUMP'S ARE COSTING FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF
THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS, TRUMP'S ARE COSTING FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700,
NUMBERS, TRUMP'S ARE COSTING FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700,
NUMBERS, TRUMP'S ARE COSTING FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AN
NUMBERS, TRUMP'S ARE COSTING FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND
NUMBERS, TRUMP'S ARE COSTING FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT
NUMBERS, TRUMP'S ARE COSTING FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS
NUMBERS, TRUMP'S ARE COSTING FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS BEFORE
NUMBERS, TRUMP'S ARE COSTING FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS
NUMBERS, TRUMP'S ARE COSTING FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS ILLEGAL
FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS ILLEGAL
FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS ILLEGAL WAR
FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS ILLEGAL WAR I
FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS ILLEGAL WAR IN
FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS ILLEGAL WAR IN IRAN
FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS ILLEGAL WAR IN IRAN PUSHED
FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS ILLEGAL WAR IN IRAN PUSHED PRICES
FAMILIES AN AVERAGE OF $1700, AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS ILLEGAL WAR IN IRAN PUSHED PRICES EVEN
AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS ILLEGAL WAR IN IRAN PUSHED PRICES EVEN
AND THAT WAS BEFORE HIS ILLEGAL WAR IN IRAN PUSHED PRICES EVEN HIGHER.
WAR IN IRAN PUSHED PRICES EVEN HIGHER.
WAR IN IRAN PUSHED PRICES EVEN HIGHER. AMBASSADOR
WAR IN IRAN PUSHED PRICES EVEN HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER,
WAR IN IRAN PUSHED PRICES EVEN HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER
WAR IN IRAN PUSHED PRICES EVEN HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A
WAR IN IRAN PUSHED PRICES EVEN HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR
HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR
HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO,
HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU
HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU SAT
HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU SAT IN
HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS
HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY
HIGHER. AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM,
AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM,
AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM, AND
AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM, AND MY
AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM, AND MY DEMOCRATIC
AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM, AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES
AMBASSADOR GREER, OVER A YEAR AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM, AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND
AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM, AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND
AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM, AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND I
AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM, AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND I ASKED
AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM, AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND I ASKED YOU
AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM, AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND I ASKED YOU ABOUT
AGO, YOU SAT IN THIS VERY ROOM, AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S
AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S
AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC
AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC ACROSS
AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS
AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND
AND MY DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES AND I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID
I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID
I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY
I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL
I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL DRIVE
I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL DRIVE U
I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL DRIVE UP
I ASKED YOU ABOUT TRUMP'S CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES.
CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES.
CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES. YOU
CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES. YOU SAID,
CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES. YOU SAID, NO,
CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES. YOU SAID, NO, WE
CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES. YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN
CHAOTIC ACROSS TARIFFS AND SAID THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES. YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE
THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES. YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE
THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES. YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE TARIFFS
THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES. YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE TARIFFS AND
THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES. YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE TARIFFS AND LOWER
THEY WILL DRIVE UP PRICES. YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES.
YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES.
YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL,
YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL, NOW
YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL, NOW WE
YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL, NOW WE HAVE
YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE
YOU SAID, NO, WE CAN HAVE TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS.
TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS.
TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS. LET'S
TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS. LET'S JUST
TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS. LET'S JUST CLEAR
TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS. LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS
TARIFFS AND LOWER PRICES. WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS. LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP.
WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS. LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP.
WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS. LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP. AMBASSADOR
WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS. LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP. AMBASSADOR GREER
WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS. LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP. AMBASSADOR GREER,
WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS. LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP. AMBASSADOR GREER, HAVE
WELL, NOW WE HAVE THE RECEIPTS. LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP. AMBASSADOR GREER, HAVE TRUMPS
LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP. AMBASSADOR GREER, HAVE TRUMPS
LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP. AMBASSADOR GREER, HAVE TRUMPS TARIFFS
LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP. AMBASSADOR GREER, HAVE TRUMPS TARIFFS INCREASED
LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP. AMBASSADOR GREER, HAVE TRUMPS TARIFFS INCREASED PRICES
LET'S JUST CLEAR THIS UP. AMBASSADOR GREER, HAVE TRUMPS TARIFFS INCREASED PRICES FOR
AMBASSADOR GREER, HAVE TRUMPS TARIFFS INCREASED PRICES FOR
AMBASSADOR GREER, HAVE TRUMPS TARIFFS INCREASED PRICES FOR AMERICAN
AMBASSADOR GREER, HAVE TRUMPS TARIFFS INCREASED PRICES FOR AMERICAN FAMILIES?
TARIFFS INCREASED PRICES FOR AMERICAN FAMILIES?
TARIFFS INCREASED PRICES FOR AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR.
TARIFFS INCREASED PRICES FOR AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR. GREER:
TARIFFS INCREASED PRICES FOR AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR. GREER: SENATOR,
TARIFFS INCREASED PRICES FOR AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO.
AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO.
AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE
AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION
AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL
AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL T
AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL TO
AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6%
AMERICAN FAMILIES? MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6% YEAR
MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6% YEAR
MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6% YEAR ON
MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6% YEAR ON YEAR,
MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6% YEAR ON YEAR, MUCH
MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6% YEAR ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER
MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6% YEAR ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN
MR. GREER: SENATOR, NO. CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6% YEAR ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN
CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6% YEAR ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN
CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6% YEAR ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN JANUARY
CORE INFLATION FELL TO 2.6% YEAR ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN JANUARY 2025.
ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN JANUARY 2025.
ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN JANUARY 2025. SEN.
ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN JANUARY 2025. SEN. WARREN:
ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN JANUARY 2025. SEN. WARREN: S
ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN JANUARY 2025. SEN. WARREN: SO
ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN JANUARY 2025. SEN. WARREN: SO YOU
ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN JANUARY 2025. SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE
ON YEAR, MUCH BETTER THAN IN JANUARY 2025. SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE SAYING
JANUARY 2025. SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE SAYING
JANUARY 2025. SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE SAYING WHAT
JANUARY 2025. SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE SAYING WHAT THE
JANUARY 2025. SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE SAYING WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL
JANUARY 2025. SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE SAYING WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET
SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE SAYING WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET
SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE SAYING WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE
SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE SAYING WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE AND
SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE SAYING WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE AND THE
SEN. WARREN: SO YOU ARE SAYING WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE AND THE TREASURY
WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE AND THE TREASURY
WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE AND THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S
WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE AND THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S OWN
WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE AND THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS
WHAT THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE AND THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT
OFFICE AND THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT
OFFICE AND THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES
OFFICE AND THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES ARE
OFFICE AND THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES ARE PAYING
OFFICE AND THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN
OFFICE AND THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE
DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE
DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE OF
DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE OF 1700
DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE OF 1700 DOLLARS
DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE,
DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU
DEPARTMENT'S OWN NUMBERS THAT FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE
FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE
FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE SAYING
FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE SAYING YOUR
FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE SAYING YOUR OWN
FAMILIES ARE PAYING AN AVERAGE OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE SAYING YOUR OWN CONGRESSIONAL
OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE SAYING YOUR OWN CONGRESSIONAL
OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE SAYING YOUR OWN CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET
OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE SAYING YOUR OWN CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE
OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE SAYING YOUR OWN CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T
OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE SAYING YOUR OWN CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW
OF 1700 DOLLARS MORE, YOU ARE SAYING YOUR OWN CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT
SAYING YOUR OWN CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT
SAYING YOUR OWN CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
SAYING YOUR OWN CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE TALKING
SAYING YOUR OWN CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT?
BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT?
BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR.
BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER:
BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M
BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED
BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED T
BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO
BUDGET OFFICE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS YOU
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT? MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT.
MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT.
MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY
MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS
MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS GIVEN
MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM
MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO
MR. GREER: I'M INTERESTED TO SEE WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME.
WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME.
WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN.
WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN:
WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY
WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE
WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN
WHAT NUMBERS YOU ARE LOOKING AT. NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT
NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT
NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT THERE
NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT THERE FOR
NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT THERE FOR AT
NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT THERE FOR AT LEAST
NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT THERE FOR AT LEAST THE
NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT THERE FOR AT LEAST THE LAST
NOBODY HAS GIVEN THEM TO ME. SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT THERE FOR AT LEAST THE LAST SIX
SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT THERE FOR AT LEAST THE LAST SIX
SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT THERE FOR AT LEAST THE LAST SIX MONTHS,
SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT THERE FOR AT LEAST THE LAST SIX MONTHS, WIDELY
SEN. WARREN: THEY HAVE BEEN OUT THERE FOR AT LEAST THE LAST SIX MONTHS, WIDELY DISTRIBUTED,
THERE FOR AT LEAST THE LAST SIX MONTHS, WIDELY DISTRIBUTED,
THERE FOR AT LEAST THE LAST SIX MONTHS, WIDELY DISTRIBUTED, BECAUSE
THERE FOR AT LEAST THE LAST SIX MONTHS, WIDELY DISTRIBUTED, BECAUSE FAMILIES
THERE FOR AT LEAST THE LAST SIX MONTHS, WIDELY DISTRIBUTED, BECAUSE FAMILIES ARE
THERE FOR AT LEAST THE LAST SIX MONTHS, WIDELY DISTRIBUTED, BECAUSE FAMILIES ARE PAYING
MONTHS, WIDELY DISTRIBUTED, BECAUSE FAMILIES ARE PAYING
MONTHS, WIDELY DISTRIBUTED, BECAUSE FAMILIES ARE PAYING MORE.
BECAUSE FAMILIES ARE PAYING MORE.
BECAUSE FAMILIES ARE PAYING MORE. THER
BECAUSE FAMILIES ARE PAYING MORE. THERE
BECAUSE FAMILIES ARE PAYING MORE. THERE IS
BECAUSE FAMILIES ARE PAYING MORE. THERE IS NO
BECAUSE FAMILIES ARE PAYING MORE. THERE IS NO SERIOUS
BECAUSE FAMILIES ARE PAYING MORE. THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST
MORE. THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST
MORE. THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND
MORE. THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND THE
MORE. THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND THE COUNTRY,
MORE. THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO
MORE. THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS
THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS
THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON
THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON THAT
THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON THAT LOOKS
THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON THAT LOOKS AT
THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON THAT LOOKS AT THE
THERE IS NO SERIOUS ECONOMIST AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON THAT LOOKS AT THE NUMBERS
AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON THAT LOOKS AT THE NUMBERS
AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON THAT LOOKS AT THE NUMBERS AND
AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON THAT LOOKS AT THE NUMBERS AND THINKS
AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON THAT LOOKS AT THE NUMBERS AND THINKS THAT
AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON THAT LOOKS AT THE NUMBERS AND THINKS THAT FAMILIES
AROUND THE COUNTRY, NO SERIOUS PERSON THAT LOOKS AT THE NUMBERS AND THINKS THAT FAMILIES ARE
PERSON THAT LOOKS AT THE NUMBERS AND THINKS THAT FAMILIES ARE
PERSON THAT LOOKS AT THE NUMBERS AND THINKS THAT FAMILIES ARE DOING
PERSON THAT LOOKS AT THE NUMBERS AND THINKS THAT FAMILIES ARE DOING BETTER.
AND THINKS THAT FAMILIES ARE DOING BETTER.
AND THINKS THAT FAMILIES ARE DOING BETTER. TRUMPS
AND THINKS THAT FAMILIES ARE DOING BETTER. TRUMPS TARIFFS
AND THINKS THAT FAMILIES ARE DOING BETTER. TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN
AND THINKS THAT FAMILIES ARE DOING BETTER. TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN THAT
DOING BETTER. TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN THAT
DOING BETTER. TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN THAT FAMILIES
DOING BETTER. TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN THAT FAMILIES HAVE
DOING BETTER. TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN THAT FAMILIES HAVE PAID
DOING BETTER. TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN THAT FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON
DOING BETTER. TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN THAT FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON AVERAGE
TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN THAT FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON AVERAGE
TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN THAT FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON AVERAGE $1700
TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN THAT FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON AVERAGE $1700 LAST
TRUMPS TARIFFS MEAN THAT FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON AVERAGE $1700 LAST YEAR.
FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON AVERAGE $1700 LAST YEAR.
FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON AVERAGE $1700 LAST YEAR. NOW
FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON AVERAGE $1700 LAST YEAR. NOW THE
FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON AVERAGE $1700 LAST YEAR. NOW THE UNITED
FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON AVERAGE $1700 LAST YEAR. NOW THE UNITED STATES
FAMILIES HAVE PAID ON AVERAGE $1700 LAST YEAR. NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME
$1700 LAST YEAR. NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME
$1700 LAST YEAR. NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT
$1700 LAST YEAR. NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS
$1700 LAST YEAR. NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS SAID
$1700 LAST YEAR. NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS SAID THAT
$1700 LAST YEAR. NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE
NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE
NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS
NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE
NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL
NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL,
NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND
NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT
NOW THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE
COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE
COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE TRUMP
COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS
COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO
COURT HAS SAID THAT THOSE TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE
TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE
TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE PEOPLE
TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE PEOPLE THEIR
TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE PEOPLE THEIR MONEY
TARIFFS WERE ILLEGAL, AND AT THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE PEOPLE THEIR MONEY BACK.
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE PEOPLE THEIR MONEY BACK.
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE PEOPLE THEIR MONEY BACK. SO
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE PEOPLE THEIR MONEY BACK. SO FAR,
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE PEOPLE THEIR MONEY BACK. SO FAR, THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE PEOPLE THEIR MONEY BACK. SO FAR, THE ADMINISTRATION
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GIVE PEOPLE THEIR MONEY BACK. SO FAR, THE ADMINISTRATION HAS
PEOPLE THEIR MONEY BACK. SO FAR, THE ADMINISTRATION HAS
PEOPLE THEIR MONEY BACK. SO FAR, THE ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN
PEOPLE THEIR MONEY BACK. SO FAR, THE ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN SLOW
PEOPLE THEIR MONEY BACK. SO FAR, THE ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN SLOW WALKING.
SO FAR, THE ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN SLOW WALKING.
SO FAR, THE ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN SLOW WALKING. AMBASSADOR
SO FAR, THE ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN SLOW WALKING. AMBASSADOR GREER,